Isis Kitcher

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Details

London
United Kingdom
07429629092
kitcher96@gmail.com

Links

Resume Website

Github

Skills

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript

Python

Django

jQuery

Git

GitHub

Heroku

Professional Summary

I'm a passionate Web Developer who'll stop at nothing, to realise my dream. For the past 3 years, I've been on a journey to find my passion. I began on Shopify building a drop-shipping store. I decided to cut costs by learning to develop all the tools myself.

My initial HTML, CSS and vanilla JS knowledge is self taught. This was tremendous help when working through my Code Institute boot-camp I joined last September. I have developed the mindset needed to ask for help, filter the internet for answers and not get discouraged when things don't go my way.

Tenacity and patience are two key skill that have found and served me well through this journey and I'm excited in seeing where this path leads me next.

Work Experience

Volunteer, Windsor Walk House Charity Shop, London

JUNE 2012 - JUNE 2014

- Design window displays to attract the gaze of potential customers.
- Price stock and arrange various donations.

Bartender, Waiter, Wimbledon Greyhound Stadium, London

DECEMBER 2015 - APRIL 2017

- Deliver high quality service to VIP guests.
- Ensure I create a comfortable vibe and memorable experiece.

Team Leader, Bartender, Compass Group, Chelsea Football Club, London

NOVEMBER 2017 - SEPTEMBER 2018

- Brief my team before each match day about their responsibilities.
- Ensure my team and I complete our tasks to a premium standard.

Barista, Thames Clippers, London

JUNE 2018 - FEBRUARY 2019

- Maintain stock levels and keep to health and safetly standards.
- Look out for suspicious packages, fire hazards, commuters who may be at risk of going overboard.
- Interact with commuters, providing information about our route and service.

Deckhand, Thames Clippers, London

FEBRUARY 2019 - PRESENT

- Ensure I keep up with safety training and documentation.
- Look after the safety of commuters, the vessel and myself.
- Fix minor issues with each vessel I am assigned to.
- Train the barista for safety drills.

Education

GCSE, St. Thomas the Apostle College, London

SEPTEMBER 2007 - SEPTEMBER 2012

8 GCSE grades including English, Science and Math.

A level, Christ The King Sixth Form College, London

SEPTEMBER 2012 - SEPTEMBER 2014

Achieved A Levels in Computer Science, Business Studies and History.

Software Engineering, Kingston University, London

SEPTEMBER 2014 - SEPTEMBER 2017

Dropped out due to personal and family problems. My family and I were going through sudden homelessness and I needed to find a steady immediate income.

Diploma in Full Stack Development, Code Institute, London

SEPTEMBER 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2022

Graduated a Fullstack focused bootcamp.

My skills were heavily developed when it came to.

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JS
- Python
- Django

Projects

Myrag, Django E-Commerce Website

https://myrag.herokuapp.com/

https://github.com/devisis/myrag

Sandra's Kitchen, Django Restaurant Booking Webapp

https://sandraskitchen.herokuapp.com/ https://github.com/devisis/sandras-kitchen

Battleships, Python Game

https://devisis-battleships.herokuapp.com/ https://github.com/devisis/battleships

Ilts Coming Home, Beginner HTML & CSS

https://devisis.github.io/its-coming-home/england.html https://github.com/devisis/its-coming-home

Rock Paper Scissors Lizard Spock, Vanilla JS

https://devisis.github.io/rock-paper-scissors-lizard-spock/ https://github.com/devisis/rock-paper-scissors-lizard-spock